articoolo.com 2017-11-04

# Articoolo

Overview

This Privacy Policy explains how Personal Information (as defined below) is collected, used, and disclosed by Articoolo. We respect your privacy and ask you to respect the privacy of others.

By using Articoolo's Services, you acknowledge and accept the policies and practices described in this Privacy Policy. You agree that you are consenting to our use and disclosure of information, and consenting to receive notifications (including by e-mail), all as further described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into the Articoolo's Terms of Use which may be found in the following link: [Terms of Use](http://articoolo.com/terms_of_use), and is an integral part thereof. If a term is capitalized and is not otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, it shall have the meaning ascribed to it in the Terms of Use.

Information Collection: Personally Identifiable Information

In the course of using Articoolo’s Services, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you and administer your use and enjoyment of our Services ("Personal Information"). Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your name, phone number and e-mail address. We use your Personal Information mainly to provide you our Services and products and administer your inquiries.

We also collect the other information that you provide, directly or indirectly, as part of registration and use of our Services (including without limitation, [zip code or location, individual preferences, purchase habits, transactional data, etc.]) ("Non-Identifying Information").

Certain Non-Identifying Information would be considered a part of your Personal Information if it were combined with other identifiers (for example, combining your zip code with your street address) in a way that enables you to be identified. But the same information can be considered Non-Identifying Information when is taken alone or combined only with other non-identifying information (for example, your viewing preferences). We may combine and analyze your Personal Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other Articoolo's users ("Analyzed Information") to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve our Services and to analyze and understand how our Services are being used.

When you access our Services via mobile device, we may collect the unique device identifier assigned to that device by phone makers, carriers, or makers of the operating system (to the extent allowed by such phone makers, carriers, or makers of the operating system) (the "Device ID").

How Do We Use Information Collected?

We use the Non-Identifying Information collected to operate and improve our Services. We will use the Personal Information to help users organize, invite, track, etc. their orders, as well enable transactions and purchases to be completed.

In order to allow you to use our Services, we may be required to verify your identity. We may, directly or through third parties, verify information you provide through certain sources or third party databases. We may also use your information to verify your identity in the event you contact us for assistance with our Services.

In certain situations, we may use or share your Personal Information in order to investigate, prevent, defend against, or take other action regarding violations of our Terms of Use, illegal activities, suspected fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the legal rights or physical safety of any person or the security of our network, to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, in an emergency, to protect the health and safety our users or the general public, or as otherwise required by law, to respond to claims regarding violation of any rights of third parties.

Analyzed Information may be used and disclosed to third parties for marketing, promotional and targeting purposes. Analyzed Information does not disclose your specific Personal Information. We may outsource some tasks to other companies or third parties and may share your information with those companies or third parties if reasonably necessary to enable them to assist in fulfilling the requests you make via our Services and other functions that require access to information you supply online. In such cases, if such affiliated companies or third parties acting on our behalf are given access to the information you have supplied to us, we require that the companies abide by our Privacy Policy and institute safeguards to protect the confidentiality of your information.

Any feedback, questions, comments, suggestions, ideas, or the like that you send to Articoolo will be treated as being non-confidential and non-proprietary, and Articoolo will be free to use such information for any purpose whatsoever including, but not limited to, developing, manufacturing, and marketing services.

If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, or in the event of a merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation, we may transfer, sell, or assign to third parties information concerning your relationship with us, including, without limitation, Personal Information that you provide and other information concerning your relationship with us. Such third parties will assume responsibility for the Personal Information collected by us in connection with our business operations and such third parties will assume the rights and obligations regarding such information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may use your Device ID for security purposes. Additionally, we may use Device IDs to monitor suspicious activity. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of Device IDs by any advertisers.

Cookies

Articoolo uses a browser feature known as cookies, which are small text files which are placed on your computer or equipment when you visit certain online pages, to track your activities, record your preferences, and make the Services and Platform more responsive to your needs by delivering a better and more personalized experience to you.

Third Parties

Our Services may utilize social networking or “share functionality” or may contain links to third party sites that are not owned or controlled by us. We have no control over any share functionality or the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party site. You are subject to the policies of those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your Personal Information to anyone. Additionally, the sites may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

We may use third party service providers to help us analyze certain online activities. We do not share any specific Personal Information about our users with these third parties, and these third parties do not collect such information on our behalf.

Security and Information Protection

We use many tools to help protect your Personal Information against unauthorized access and disclosure however, since the Internet is not a 100% secure medium for communication, we cannot guarantee that your Personal Information or private communications will always remain private when using our Services.

We are not responsible for any damages which you, or others, may suffer as a result of the loss of confidentiality of such Personal Information.

We take all reasonably necessary precautions to protect your information. To this end, all Personal Information stored by us is kept on a server in a secure environment. Only employees, our partners and any sub-contractors who need the information to perform a specific service are granted access to Personal Information.

YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK FOR YOUR USE OF OUR SERVICES AND THE INFORMATION YOU ACCESS THROUGH THE THEM.

Policy Regarding Children

Articoolo does not knowingly or specifically collect information about children under the age of 18 and believes that minors should get their parents' consent before giving out any Personal Information. A parent or guardian of a child under the age of 18 may review and request deletion of child's Personal Information as well as prohibit the use thereof.

Changing or Deleting Your Information

You may e-mail us at [contact@articoolo.com](mailto:contact@articoolo.com) with a request that we delete your Personal Information. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor your request. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes.

You may limit our use of your personal data for direct marketing purposes. You may also request access to, correction of, or deletion of personal data. For instructions on changing any of your privacy preferences, accessing your information, updating your information or for any privacy or data-protection-related questions, please write to [contact@articoolo.com](mailto:contact@articoolo.com). 

Changes to Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is subject to revisions from time to time, upon our sole discretion and without prior notice. Should you object to any such modifications, you must cease using our Services. Continued use of our Services following any such change will indicate your acknowledgement of such change and agreement to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. All such changes will apply to previously collected information. Therefore, please make sure you check this Privacy Policy regularly.

© Copyright 2015-2017 Articoolo Inc. All Rights Reserved
